U.S. Department of Labor Women's Bureau "Women's Work Counts" Posters 6071 G
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Department of Labor Women's Bureau "Women's Work Counts" Posters
1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Department of Labor
Anderson, Marty
Foster, Susan
Heavener, Becky
Honeywood, Varnette P.
Johnson, Sue
Lopez, Mary Louise
Porter, Mary
Ringgold, Faith
Smith, Jaune Quick-To-See
6071 G
0.11 cubic feet
0.1 linear ft.
Posters.
US Department of Labor Women's Bureau 75th anniversary poster series.
5791197
Scope and Contents
Large format colorful posters produced for the 75th anniversary of the US Department of Labor Women's Bureau.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
R. Miles, April 21, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, April 21, 2016
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5029m: U.S. Women's Bureau "The Employment and Unemployment of Negro Women" Manuscript 5762 mf: Records of the Women's Bureau of the US Department of Labor on Microfilm 5901 mf: Records of the Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor, Pt.2, Series A on Microfilm 5946 mf: Records of the Women's Bureau of the U.S. Department of Labor; Part II: Women in World War II; Series B. Subjects and Correspondence Files on War Industries on Microfilm
Anderson, Marty; Foster, Susan; Heavener, Becky; Honeywood, Varnette P.; Johnson, Sue; Lopez, Mary Louise; Porter, Mary; Ringgold, Faith; Smith, Jaune Quick-To-See; United States. Women's Bureau; United States. Department of Labor
5791197
- USDL, Women's Bureau, 1995 (Folder 1)
  - Three Working Women, 1995; 1 (Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Stylized depiction of factory, clerical, and professional women. Original artwork by Becky Heavener.
  - Women and Children, 1995; 2 (Folder 1)
    Original artwork by Faith Ringgold
  - Woman/Mother Doing Housework, 1995; 3 (Folder 1)
    Original artwork by Mary Porter
  - Waitress, 1995; 4 (Folder 1)
    Original artwork by Varnette P. Honeywood
  - Native American Women, 1995; 5 (Folder 1)
    Depicted in advertising around a piece of Native American clothing. Original artwork by Jaune Quick-To-See Smith.
  - Mother and Child, 1995; 6 (Folder 1)
    Original artwork by Susan Foster.
  - Various Tools, 1995; 7 (Folder 1)
    Pen, wrench, hammer, airplane, etc. Original artwork by Lonni Sue Johnson.
  - Mother and Child, 1995; 8 (Folder 1)
    Central or South Native American. Original artwork by Mary Louise Lopez.
  - Office Work, 1995; 9 (Folder 1)
    Original artwork by Marty Anderson.